<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Strattons in Japan</title>
    <link>https://jimmytortilla.github.io/thestrattons/</link>
    <description>Recent content on The Strattons in Japan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 23:24:50 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jimmytortilla.github.io/thestrattons/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Strattons</title>
      <link>https://jimmytortilla.github.io/thestrattons/about/our_story/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 23:24:50 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jimmytortilla.github.io/thestrattons/about/our_story/</guid>
      <description>Nathan (Nate) and Azusa met in Eugene, Oregon in late spring of 2000: He was a student at Eugene Bible College, working on his bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in missionary studies after having spent two years as a short-term missionary in a church in Yokohama, Japan. She was in the U.S. taking classes at Lane Community College and then later at Eugene Bible College, working on improving her English skills and learning about ministry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hopes and Plans</title>
      <link>https://jimmytortilla.github.io/thestrattons/about/hopes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 22:31:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jimmytortilla.github.io/thestrattons/about/hopes/</guid>
      <description>Azusa and I (and presumably the kids, too) are excited about the future. We have had a few setbacks&amp;ndash;only from the human perspective&amp;ndash;but absolutely no setbacks from God&amp;rsquo;s point of view. He is in total loving control, working out all things according to His good and perfect purposes. We rest in that truth as we try to walk in obedience each day.
For now our hope and plan is to use the time and resources that God has provided us during this season to continue to encourage our brothers and sisters in Siloam Church and beyond, to share the gospel whenever we have opportunities, and to grow in the knowledge of gospel of Jesus Christ.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moving</title>
      <link>https://jimmytortilla.github.io/thestrattons/post/prayer_news07172019/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jimmytortilla.github.io/thestrattons/post/prayer_news07172019/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;ve moved &amp;hellip; again! This week&amp;rsquo;s move makes the second move since the end of March when we moved into the Waifu House.
These past several months have been busy with a lot of cleaning, sorting, disposing of, packing, and moving&amp;ndash;all times two! It has been a time for all of us to realize how much stuff and things can be a hindrance. Azusa and I in particular have felt at times ashamed of how many unnecessary items we have collected over the years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>House-Cleaning</title>
      <link>https://jimmytortilla.github.io/thestrattons/post/prayer_news07102019/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jimmytortilla.github.io/thestrattons/post/prayer_news07102019/</guid>
      <description>Since late March of this year, in preparation for our (then) anticipated trip to the U.S. in order to join the summer conferences with ABWE and begin pre-field, our family has lived in what I call the Waifu (pronounced &amp;ldquo;wife&amp;rdquo;) House&amp;ndash;named thus for its location in the neighborhood of Waifu in Kikuchi City, Japan. This house was purchased by an ABWE missionary for the purpose of supporting other missionaries and interns.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visa Challenges</title>
      <link>https://jimmytortilla.github.io/thestrattons/post/prayer_news06152019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jimmytortilla.github.io/thestrattons/post/prayer_news06152019/</guid>
      <description>The picture above was taken from our airplane window on our way home from a trip to Naha on the island of Okinawa. It was not a pleasure trip. It was a trip Azusa and I took for Azusa to obtain a visa in order to, at least in our minds at the time, begin our journey into pre-field with ABWE.
We had not anticipated Azusa having any problems getting her visa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reach Out</title>
      <link>https://jimmytortilla.github.io/thestrattons/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jimmytortilla.github.io/thestrattons/contact/</guid>
      <description>We would love to hear from you. If you want to write the old-fashioned way, here is our mailing address in Japan:
1333-5 Sugi, Yamaga-Shi, Kumamoto-Ken, Japan 861-0552
Or you can write by filling in the form boxes below and pressing the Send button.
*NOTE: By using the contact forms below you consent to allowing us to use your email address to respond to you. Our contact forms use a third party service called Formspree.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>