<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Our Story on The Strattons in Japan</title>
    <link>https://stratton.life/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Our Story on The Strattons in Japan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 23:24:50 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://stratton.life/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Strattons</title>
      <link>https://stratton.life/about/our_story/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 23:24:50 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stratton.life/about/our_story/</guid>
      <description>Nathan (Nate) and Azusa met in Eugene, Oregon in late spring of 2000: He was a student at Eugene Bible College, working on his bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in missionary studies after having spent two years as a short-term missionary in a church in Yokohama, Japan. She was in the U.S. taking classes at Lane Community College and then later at Eugene Bible College, working on improving her English skills and learning about ministry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hopes and Plans</title>
      <link>https://stratton.life/about/hopes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 22:31:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stratton.life/about/hopes/</guid>
      <description>Azusa and I (and presumably the kids, too) are excited about the future. We have had a few setbacks&amp;ndash;only from the human perspective&amp;ndash;but absolutely no setbacks from God&amp;rsquo;s point of view. He is in total loving control, working out all things according to His good and perfect purposes. We rest in that truth as we try to walk in obedience each day.
For now our hope and plan is to use the time and resources that God has provided us during this season to continue to encourage our brothers and sisters in Siloam Church and beyond, to share the gospel whenever we have opportunities, and to grow in the knowledge of gospel of Jesus Christ.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>